<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Certifications on Advaith Achanta</title>
    <link>https://Advaith2049.github.io/portfolio_website/projects/contributions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Certifications on Advaith Achanta</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 16:49:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Advaith2049.github.io/portfolio_website/projects/contributions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data Analytics Consulting Virtual Internship</title>
      <link>https://Advaith2049.github.io/portfolio_website/projects/contributions/kpmg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Advaith2049.github.io/portfolio_website/projects/contributions/kpmg/</guid>
      <description>The Data Analytics Consulting Virtual Internship by KPMG was my initial guide into the world of data analytics.
The entire experience was divided into three modules - Data Quality Assessment, Data Insights, and Presentation.
Data Quality Assessment dealed with the preparation and cleaning of data to get it ready for analysis. A dataset related to bicycle sales was provided.
Data Insights involved figuring out the high value customers based on customer demographics and attributes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solutions Architect Virtual Experience Program</title>
      <link>https://Advaith2049.github.io/portfolio_website/projects/contributions/aws/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 17:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Advaith2049.github.io/portfolio_website/projects/contributions/aws/</guid>
      <description>The AWS Solutions Architect Virtual Experience Program was an insightful and detailed look into understanding the work of a Solutions Architect.
The Program gave a wonderful opportunity to put myself in the shoes of an Architect and perform tasks that simulated the real life work.
The main aim of the module was to design a simple, scalable, hosting architecture and compile it as a letter to the client.
The task gave me an understanding of the various services that AWS provides like CodePipeline, RDS, and Elastic Load Balancing among others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science And Machine Learning Internship</title>
      <link>https://Advaith2049.github.io/portfolio_website/projects/contributions/unp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 17:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Advaith2049.github.io/portfolio_website/projects/contributions/unp/</guid>
      <description>The Data Science &amp;amp; Machine Learning Internship provided by UNP (United Network of Professionals) was an excellent introduction to the foundational topics of data science.
It initially tackled the basics of Python language, and informed about various aspects like lists, loops, and several packages including pandas, numpy, and seaborn among others.
The course futher progressed to introducing datasets into picture, on which we were supposed to apply basic algorithms like linear regression and logistic regression.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
