<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Machine Learning on Advaith Achanta</title>
    <link>https://Advaith2049.github.io/portfolio_website/tags/machine-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Machine Learning on Advaith Achanta</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 17:08:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Advaith2049.github.io/portfolio_website/tags/machine-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data Science And Machine Learning Internship</title>
      <link>https://Advaith2049.github.io/portfolio_website/projects/contributions/unp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 17:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Advaith2049.github.io/portfolio_website/projects/contributions/unp/</guid>
      <description>The Data Science &amp;amp; Machine Learning Internship provided by UNP (United Network of Professionals) was an excellent introduction to the foundational topics of data science.
It initially tackled the basics of Python language, and informed about various aspects like lists, loops, and several packages including pandas, numpy, and seaborn among others.
The course futher progressed to introducing datasets into picture, on which we were supposed to apply basic algorithms like linear regression and logistic regression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Used Car Price Prediction using Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://Advaith2049.github.io/portfolio_website/projects/creations/car_price/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Advaith2049.github.io/portfolio_website/projects/creations/car_price/</guid>
      <description>Used Car Price Prediction: An Overview Cleaned the dataset, removed outliers, and pre-processed the data in a format suitable to the objective
Performed extensive EDA or Exploratory Data Analysis to understand the relationships between the variables and data points
Fit the processed data into various models including Linear Regression, Random Forest, KNN, SVM, among several other algorithms, to make predictions and arrive at the best model through comparison
Charted a comparison table for the ease of determining the best model and accuracy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank Term Deposit Prediction using Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://Advaith2049.github.io/portfolio_website/projects/creations/term_deposit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Advaith2049.github.io/portfolio_website/projects/creations/term_deposit/</guid>
      <description>Bank Term Deposit Prediction: An Overview Cleaned the dataset, removed outliers, and pre-processed the data in a format suitable to the objective
Performed extensive EDA or Exploratory Data Analysis to understand the relationships between the variables and data points
Fit the processed data into various models including Logistic Regression, Random Forest, KNN, SVM, among several other algorithms, to make predictions and arrive at the best model through comparison
Charted a comparison table for the ease of determining the best model and accuracy</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
